<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<concept id="NetworkExplorer-UserInterface-CriteriaBuilder">
    <title>Criteria Builder</title>
    <conbody>
        <section>
            <title>Overview</title>
            <p>
                Criteria Builder allows you to define/build criteria for searching through nodes, and managed objects using
                a graphically represented criteria tree.
            </p>

            <p>
                To switch to Criteria Builder, click on the <b>Switch to Criteria Builder</b> button on the right
                side of the search box. A <b>Node Type</b> dropdown and a <b>Node Name</b> text box are displayed.
                If you enter a query string into the search box, the query string is discarded if you switch to Criteria
                Builder.
                Any query results returned in the Results table, are still displayed on the screen after switching to
                Criteria Builder.
            </p>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>Search by Node</title>
            <p>
                To search for nodes, click the <b>Node Type</b> dropdown and select a node type. You can further refine your search results by providing a
                name in the <b>Node Name</b> text field. You can only specify a single name or a partial name. Space, Comma and quote are not accepted in the node name.
                A search using only the <b>Node Name</b> can be carried out by providing a
                <b>Node Name</b> and leaving the <b>Node Type</b> dropdown empty. Click the <b>Search</b> button to execute your search.
            </p>
            <p>Note : Partial names supported examples are LTE01* and *TE01 to get accurate results. Such as LTE*01 is not supported</p>
            <p>
                When a node search is executed and a corresponding node exists, a Managed Object is returned to
                represent that node. Managed Objects are returned in the following order:
                <ol>
                    <li>MeContext</li>
                    <li>ManagedElement</li>
                    <li>NetworkElement</li>
                </ol>
            </p>
            <p>
                Each node will only return a single Managed Object instance to avoid duplication. For example:
                <ul>
                    <li>
                        If a node has no MeContext but has ManagedElement and NetworkElement, ManagedElement
                        is returned, as this is the highest precedence type available.
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        If a node has all three instances available, MeContext will be returned, as this is
                        the highest precedence type available.
                    </li>
                </ul>
            </p>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>Building a Managed Object Query</title>
            <p>
                To search for Managed Objects, first select a node type then click the <b>+ Has Child</b> button. Another dropdown
                is displayed, with a list of Managed Object types. Select the Managed Object type you want to search for.
                If the selected object has children, a <b>+ Has Child</b> button is displayed below the object
                select box. To add another object, click the <b>+ Has Child</b> button.
                Click the <b>Search</b> button to execute your search. All objects
                included in the Criteria Builder will be displayed in the table. This will not return the Managed
                Objects representing the nodes, unless you search for those Managed Object types specifically.
                You can delete the object added by clicking the trash icon.
            </p>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title id="searchByChildren">Search by Children</title>
            <p>
                After adding a Managed Object, you can add child criteria, if the object selected has
                children. If the selected object has children, a <b>+ Has Child</b> button is displayed below the object
                select box. Clicking this will produce another select box that branches from the previous object. In
                this select box, select a Managed Object. If a Managed Object (MO) has more than one
                namespace attribute, the Managed Object name will be be repeated in the list.
                The MO will be differentiated when you  hover the mouse over the item to display the name and namespace value in a tooltip.
                Click the <b>Search</b> button to execute your search. All objects included in the Criteria Builder will be displayed in the table.
            </p>
            <p>
                To delete a child which you have added, click the trash can icon. Deleting an object will also delete
                child objects.
            </p>
            <image href="../resources/images/Mo_toolTip.png"/>
            <p>
                For YANG based nodes, in dropdown you will see some duplicate Managed Objects and tree structure upto
                that Managed Object name separated by <b>|</b> symbol. When you hover the mouse cursor over the item
                a full tree structure and namespace of that Managed Object is displayed in tooltip. After selection of item, it is displayed with $$ in between in textbox.
            </p>
            <image href="../resources/images/MOtooltip.png"/>
            <p>
                <b>Note:</b> Some child Managed Object types in the dropdown list might be disabled. This can occur where
                a child Managed Object is incompatible with any of its parents due to the parent having different namespace versions.
                Child Managed Objects are filtered out and disabled where the namespace versions are
                different to its parent Managed Object.
                If this occurs the Managed Object types are colored grey. It is not be possible to select them
                from the dropdown options.
                An example of a Managed Object with disabled child nodes is ManagedElement for the node type MINI-LINK-Indoor.
            </p>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>Search by Attributes</title>
            <p>
                Attribute criteria can be added to a Managed Object. Click <b>+ Add Criteria</b> button and select
                an attribute in the first dropdown displayed. The default comparator is set to <b>Any Value</b>. This will
                add an additional column to the results. This shows the value of the specified attribute for each result.
                If you select a comparator value, an additional input field or select box is presented. This narrows the
                search results to a more specific set.
            </p>
            <image href="../resources/images/attributeCriteria.png"/>
            <p>
                Searching by attributes also supports the wildcard operator at the start and/or end of the
                attribute value. For example, if you wanted all EUtranCellFDD objects with a EUtranCellFDDId that starts with
                "Cell", you would put Cell* in the attribute input box. There is a maximum of 3 wildcard value searches
                supported per search execution. Using more than 3 wildcards will result in slower queries, and less
                specific search results. Click the <b>Done</b> button to enable the <b>Search</b> button.
            </p>
            <p>
                For YANG based nodes, there may be duplicate ENUM members for some attributes. Duplicate ENUM members belonging
                to different namespace are distinguished when you hover mouse cursor over the item description and namespace
                is displayed in tooltip.
            </p>
            <image href="../resources/images/attribute_tooltip.PNG"/>
            <p>
                Once you click on <b>Done</b> button, attribute and selected value are displayed below textbox. This text has namespace as prefix to selected value.
            </p>
            <image href="../resources/images/selected_duplicate_enum.png" />
            <p>
                Click the search button to execute the search. You can modify existing criteria by clicking
                <b>+ Add/Edit Criteria</b> button on the managed object.
            </p>
            <p>
                <b>Note:</b> If different versions of Managed Objects have different attributes, they are all listed in Criteria Builder.
                Search results will only be returned for Managed Object versions that have the selected attribute(s).
            </p>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>Search by Enum List Attributes</title>
            <p>
                To add a criteria attribute to a managed object click <b>+ Add Criteria</b> button and select
                an attribute from the first dropdown displayed. The default comparator is set to <b>Any Value</b>. Changing the comparator to either <b>Contains Any Of</b> or <b>Contains All Of</b>
                adds an additional multi-value select box. This allows for the selection of more than one value. This also narrows the
                search results to a more specific set.
                Click the <b>Done</b> button to enable the <b>Search</b> button.
            </p>
            <image href="../resources/images/listCriteriaAttribute.png"/>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>Search by Boolean List Attributes</title>
            <p>
                To add a criteria attribute to a managed object click <b>+ Add Criteria</b> button and select
                an attribute from the first dropdown displayed. The default comparator is set to <b>Any Value</b>. Change the comparator to either <b>Contains Any Of</b> or <b>Contains All Of</b>
                to add an additional multi-value select box. This allows for the selection of more than one value. This also narrows the search results to a more specific set.
                Click the <b>Done</b> button to enable the <b>Search</b> button.
            </p>
            <image href="../resources/images/BooleanListCriteriaAttributes.png"/>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>Search by Primitive List Attributes</title>
            <p>
                To add a criteria attribute to a managed object click <b>+ Add Criteria</b> button and select
                an attribute from the first dropdown displayed. The default comparator is set to <b>Any Value</b>. Change the comparator to either <b>Contains Any Of</b> or <b>Contains All Of</b>
                to add an input field. This field allows for the creation of Values for each of the user-inputted values.
                This is done by typing a value and then pressing the enter key.
                This also narrows the search results to a more specific set.
            </p>
            <image href="../resources/images/primitiveListCriteriaAttributes.png"/>
            <p>
                Search by primitive list attributes to query more than one value. A new Pill is required for
                each value that needs to be queried.
                Click the <b>Done</b> button to enable the <b>Search</b> button.
            </p>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>Search by Struct Attributes</title>
            <p>
                To add a criteria attribute to a managed object click <b>+ Add Criteria</b> button and select
                an struct attribute from the first dropdown displayed. You can then select a child attribute under the struct attribute in the second dropdown.
                When the child attribute is selected, the default comparator is set to <b>Any Value</b>.
                If you select a comparator value, an additional input field or select box is displayed.
                This narrows the search results to a more specific set.
                Click the <b>Done</b> button to enable the <b>Search</b> button.
            </p>
            <image href="../resources/images/structCriteriaAttribute.png"/>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>Search by Multiple Attributes</title>
            <p>
                Click <b>Add More Criteria</b>, to add more attribute criteria to the object (each criteria may be of a
                different attribute type). You can either use the "and" conjunction or the "or" conjunction to chain
                together your attributes. The default is "and". For example, if you added attributes ENodeBFunctionId
                and eNBId to Managed Object ENodeBFunction using the "and" conjunction it would produce a query similar
                to the following:
            </p>
            <ul>
                <li>
                    <i>
                        select all objects of type ENodeBFunction where ENodeBFunction has attr ENodeBFunctionId = id
                        <b>and</b> attr eNBId = 50 from node type ERBS
                    </i>
                </li>
            </ul>
            <p>
                The results would then show all instances of ENodeBFunction where ENodeBFunctionId = id <b>AND</b> eNBId = 50.
                If you added ENodeBFunctionId and eNBId to ENodeBFunction using the "or" conjunction it would produce
                a query similar to the following:
            </p>
            <ul>
                <li>
                    <i>
                        select all objects of type ENodeBFunction where ENodeBFunction has attr ENodeBFunctionId = id
                        <b>or</b> attr eNBId = 50 from node type ERBS
                    </i>
                </li>
            </ul>
            <p>
                The results would then show any instance of ENodeBFunction where ENodeBFunctionId = id <b>OR</b> eNBId = 50
            </p>
            <p>
                Attributes with "Any Value" set cannot use the "or" conjunction. The attribute column for dscpLabel
                is displayed in the results table. The number of results returned is not affected.
            </p>
            <p>
                <b>Note:</b> A maximum of two attributes with the "or" conjunction is allowed per query.
            </p>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>Show or Hide Objects in Results Table</title>
            <p>
                By default, objects added using Criteria Builder will be shown in the results table.
                To hide these objects from your results, click the eye icon next to the object. The icon changes to
                an eye with a line through it to indicate that the object is hidden from the results table. To
                display these objects in your results again, click the eye icon with the line through it. Click the <b>Search</b>
                button to update the Results table. Any criteria you have selected for an object is displayed in the
                results table. At least one object must be selected before you can execute a query.
            </p>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>Switch Back to Search</title>
            <p>
                You can switch from Criteria Builder to regular search at any time. To make this switch,
                click the <b>Switch to Search Box</b> button located next to the <b>Search</b> button. If Criteria Builder
                has valid criteria added, the search box will be populated with the query built in the Criteria Builder.
            </p>
            <p>
                Query results returned as a result of executing Criteria Builder search will remain on the screen after
                switching back to the search box.
            </p>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>Delete Criteria</title>
            <p>
                To delete criteria added to an object, click the <b>+ Add/Edit Criteria</b> button and click the trash
                can icon next to the criteria you want to delete.
            </p>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>Clear Criteria Builder</title>
            <p>
                To clear all criteria from Criteria Builder, click the <b>Clear Query</b> button in the top right corner
                of Criteria Builder.
            </p>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>Compatibility</title>
            <p>
                Not all Managed Objects and criteria attributes are compatible. If Managed Objects or attributes
                lower in the Criteria Builder are incompatible with ones higher up, then the tree hierarchy is
                updated accordingly.
            </p>
        </section>
    </conbody>
</concept>
