<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<concept id="NetworkExplorer-Tutorials-SavedSearches">
    <title>Manage Saved Searches</title>
    <conbody>
        <section>
            <title>Locate Saved Search</title>
            <p>
                To locate a Saved Search, click on the Saved Search name in the Saved Searches Tab. Clicking on a Saved Search in the Tab will display the Saved Search
                details, and populate the results table with the search results. Saved Searches and applicable actions can be located by
                clicking the "Saved Search Management".
            </p>
            <image href="../resources/images/NetworkExplorer_childSavedSearch.png"/>
            <p> Here, the Saved Search Management page displays all of the existing Saved Searches
                that the user is allowed to view. For a detailed description of this page refer to the
                <xref scope="external" href="#help/app/savedsearchmanagement/topic/ui/savedSearches">Saved Search Management Page</xref> section.
            </p>
            <p>
                Saved Searches can either be saved as public or private. Private Saved Searches can be viewed by
                the user that created them if they have the capability SavedSearch_Private:read, or by other users who have the capability SavedSearchOthers_Private:read.
                Public Saved Searches can be viewed by the owner if they have the capability SavedSearch_Public:read, or by other users who have the capability SavedSearchOthers_Public:read.
                If a public Saved Search has the same name as one of your private Saved Searches, the sidebar will include the sharing
                permission in brackets after the name of each.
            </p>
            <p>
                Alternatively, the contents of a Saved Search can be returned by entering its name in the search box.
                Should a private and public Saved Search of the same name exist in the system, the private Saved Search
                will be returned. Therefore, the process outlined in the paragraph above should be used to return a
                public Saved Search where a private Saved Search exists of the same name.
            </p>
        </section>
    </conbody>
</concept>
