<concept id="NetworkExplorer-searchForManagedObjectsWithAChild">
    <title>Searching for Managed Objects where a Managed Object has a Child</title>
    <conbody>
        <section>
            <p>
                To return specific children of a managed object, you can specify child and parent
                types using the following syntax, replacing [PARENT MO TYPE] and [CHILD MO TYPE] with the desired types:
            </p>
            <codeblock>
                [TYPE] where [PARENT MO TYPE] has child [CHILD MO TYPE]
            </codeblock>
            <p>
                The shorthand version to return specific children of a managed object omits the child keyword, you can
                specify child and parent
                types using the following syntax, replacing [PARENT MO TYPE] and [CHILD MO TYPE] with the desired types:
            </p>
            <codeblock>
                [TYPE] where [PARENT MO TYPE] has [CHILD MO TYPE]
            </codeblock>
            <p>
                [TYPE] can be either [PARENT MO TYPE] or [CHILD MO TYPE]. [CHILD MO TYPE] can be either child or
                grandchild of [PARENT MO TYPE]. For example:
            </p>
            <codeblock>
                ENodeBFunction where ENodeBFunction has child EUtranCellFDD
            </codeblock>
            <p>
                Specify multiple children using the following syntax:
            </p>
            <codeblock>
                [TYPE] where [PARENT MO TYPE] has child [CHILD MO TYPE] and [CHILD MO TYPE] has child [GRAND
            </codeblock>
            <codeblock>
                ENodeBFunction where ENodeBFunction has child EUtranCellFDD and EUtranCellFDD has child EUtranFreqRelation
            </codeblock>
            <p>
                Search child and parent Managed Objects by attributes and name using the following syntax:
            </p>
            <codeblock>
                [TYPE] where [PARENT MO TYPE] has child [CHILD MO TYPE] and object [PARENT MO TYPE] has attr [ATTRIBUTE_NAME] [OPERATOR] [ATTRIBUTE_VALUE]
            </codeblock>
            <codeblock>
                ENodeBFunction where ENodeBFunction has child EUtranCellFDD and object ENodeBFunction has attr ENodeBFunctionId = ID2
            </codeblock>
            <p>
                You can shorten the syntax when searching for an attribute of a child using the keyword WITH.
            </p>
            <codeblock>
                [TYPE] where [PARENT MO TYPE] has child [CHILD MO TYPE] with [ATTRIBUTE_NAME] [OPERATOR] [ATTRIBUTE_VALUE]
            </codeblock>
            <codeblock>
                EUtranCellRelation where EUtranCellFDD <b>has child</b> EUtranCellRelation with name = Cell1
            </codeblock>
            <p>
                The longer version of the query to get all EUtranCellRelations which are children of EUtranCellFDD is
                the
                following:
            </p>
            <codeblock>
                EUtranCellRelation where EUtranCellFDD <b>has child</b> EUtranFreqRelation and EUtranFreqRelation <b>has child</b> EUtranCellRelation and EUtranCellRelation has attr name=Cell1
            </codeblock>
            <p>
                You also can search by multiple children. Network Explorer supports up to 5 levels.
            </p>
        </section>
    </conbody>
</concept>
