<concept id="NetworkExplorer-searchForManagedObjectsWithAParent">
    <title>Searching for Managed Objects where a Managed Object has a Parent</title>
    <conbody>
        <section>
            <p>
                To query for Managed Objects with a specific parent type, use the following syntax, replacing
                [TYPE] with the desired object type, and [PARENT_TYPE] with the desired parent type:
            </p>
            <codeblock>
                [TYPE] where object [TYPE] has parent [PARENT_TYPE]
            </codeblock>
            <p>
                For example, to search for all EUtranCellFDD cells with an ENodeBFunction parent, the following query
                could be used:
            </p>
            <codeblock>
                EUtranCellFDD where EUtranCellFDD <b>has parent</b> ENodeBFunction
            </codeblock>
            <p>
                You can also filter parents by attributes and name using the following syntax:
            </p>
            <codeblock>
                [TYPE] where object [TYPE] has parent [PARENT] and object [PARENT] has attr [ATTRIBUTE_NAME] [OPERATOR] [ATTRIBUTE_VALUE]
            </codeblock>
            <p>
                For example to search for all ManagedElement objects which have MeContext parents which have an
                MeContextId of 1, the following query could be used:
            </p>
            <codeblock>
                ManagedElement where object ManagedElement <b>has parent</b> MeContext and object MeContext <b>has attr</b>
            </codeblock>
            <p>
                You can also shorten the syntax using the keyword WITH.
            </p>
            <codeblock>
                [TYPE] where object [TYPE] has parent [PARENT] with [ATTRIBUTE_NAME] [OPERATOR] [ATTRIBUTE_VALUE]
            </codeblock>
            <codeblock>
                ManagedElement where object ManagedElement <b>has parent</b> MeContext <b>with</b> MeContextId = 1
            </codeblock>
            <p>
                You can search by multiple parents, Network Explorer supports up to 5 levels.
            </p>
            <p>
                The long hand version of the
                <b>parent</b>
                syntax is as follows:
            </p>
            <codeblock>
                [TYPE] where object [TYPE] has parent [PARENT_TYPE_LEVEL_1] and object [PARENT_TYPE_LEVEL_1] has parent [PARENT_TYPE_LEVEL_2]
            </codeblock>
            <p>
                For example to search for all ENodeBFunction objects which have ManagedElement parents and the
                ManagedElement objects have MeContext parents, the following query could be used:
            </p>
            <codeblock>
                ENodeBFunction where object ENodeBFunction has parent ManagedElement and object ManagedElement has parent MeContext
            </codeblock>
        </section>
    </conbody>
</concept>
