<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<concept id="NetworkExplorer-OtherApps">
    <title>Viewing and editing a Network Object's attributes</title>
    <conbody>
        <section>
            <title>Viewing a network object's Attributes</title>
            <p>
                The attribute properties of a node can be viewed or edited in the panel on the right hand side of the
                Network Explorer main page. This panel is known as the Details panel.
            </p>
            <p>
                The Details panel is displayed by default. If it is not visible, you can make it appear by clicking the
                information icon in the top right hand side of the Action Bar. To dismiss the Details panel click the
                information icon or the close button.
            </p>
            <p>
                <b>Selecting a network object</b>
            </p>
            <p>
                To view a network object's attributes, select a row in the results table.
            </p>
            <p>
                <b>Selecting multiple network objects</b>
            </p>
            <p>
                If multiple network objects are selected, The last selected network object's attributes will be
                retrieved and displayed in the Details panel. If the last selected network object is deselected
                the Details panel will display the attributes for the second last network object that was selected.
                If the process of deselecting the last selected network object is repeated, the Details panel will be
                updated each time with the previously selected network object's attributes. This behaviour will continue
                until all network objects have been deselected.
            </p>
            <p>
                <b>Selecting all network objects</b>
            </p>
            <p>
                If the table header checkbox is used to select all network objects, then the Details panel will display
                the attributes for the last network object in the table.
            </p>
            <p>
                For more information on viewing a network object's attributes see the
                <xref scope="external" href="#help/app/topologybrowser/topic/tutorials/tutorial2">View Attribute Details</xref>
                tutorial in Topology Browser's help.
            </p>
            <p>
                TCIM (Transport Common Information Model) Model Description document details information on the managed objects, attributes and relationships.
            </p>
            <p>
                See TCIM Model Description document, 3/15519-CNA 403 3141. This is available in ENM CPI Library, EN/LZN 703 0205 R95A
            </p>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>Editing a Network Object's Attributes</title>
            <p>
                The Details panel allows editing of a network object's attributes.
            </p>
            <p>
                For more information on editing an a network object's attributes see the
                <xref scope="external" href="#help/app/topologybrowser/topic/tutorials/tutorial3">Edit Attribute Details</xref>
                tutorial in Topology Browser's help.
            </p>
        </section>
    </conbody>
</concept>