<task id="NetworkExplorer-CollectionFromSearchResults">
    <title>Add a Managed Object(s) to a Collection from Search Results</title>
    <taskbody>
        <prereq>
            <ul>
                <li>You have a Managed Object to add.</li>
                <li>
                    There is limit imposed on the maximum number of objects that can be added to a Collection. If the
                    number of selected objects being added to a new or existing Collection exceeds this limit an
                    error dialog is displayed. The default limit is 25,000 objects.
                    Note: If you require a change to the collection size limit, contact your system administrator.
                </li>
                <li>
                    You have appropriate access rights to modify a Collection. You can modify your public or
                    private Collections. An Administrator can modify other user's public Collections. See
                    <xref href="../../prerequisites.xml" type="concept">Prerequisites</xref>
                    for user role details.
                </li>
            </ul>
        </prereq>
        <context>
            <p>
                <b>Objective</b>
            </p>
            <p>
                This tutorial describes how to add Managed Object(s) (MO) to a new or existing Collection from search
                results.
            </p>
            <b>Outline</b>
            <ol>
                <li>
                    <xref type="task" href="#1">Select MO(s) from the Results Table</xref>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <xref type="task" href="#2">Add the MO(s) to a Collection</xref>
                </li>
                <li>
                    <xref type="task" href="#3">Save a Collection</xref>
                </li>
            </ol>
        </context>
        <steps>
            <step id="1">
                <cmd>Select MO(s) from the Results Table</cmd>
                <info>
                    <ol>
                        <li>
                            In the Network Explorer <b>Results Table</b>, click the row to make a single selection.
                            Multiple selections can be made by clicking the checkboxes of the MO(s) you want to return.
                            You can select MO ranges by clicking the first item, then hold shift and click the last.
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            The rows clicked and all rows in between are selected. You can select all the MOs in the
                            table by clicking the checkbox in the table header.
                        </li>
                    </ol>
                </info>
            </step>
            <step id="2">
                <cmd>Add the MO(s) to a Collection</cmd>
                <info>
                    <ol>
                        <li>
                            Click the <b>Add to a Collection</b> button in the <b>Action Bar</b>. A
                            <b>Flyout Panel</b>
                            is displayed.
                            The MO(s) can be added to a new or existing Collection
                        </li>
                        <li>To add the MO(s) to a new Collection, click the <b>Add to a new Collection</b> radio
                            button
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            Enter a Collection name. This field is mandatory. You cannot use the name of a Collection
                            or
                            Managed Object type that already exists. You can only use alphanumeric characters
                            (A-Z, a-z and 0-9), spaces and certain special characters. The supported special characters
                            are:
                            <codeblock>
                                <b>. - _</b>
                            </codeblock>
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            Click the <b>private</b> or <b>public</b> sharing permissions radio button. The default
                            value
                            is private.
                        </li>
                    </ol>
                    <p>
                        Or
                    </p>
                    <ol>
                        <li>
                            To add the MO(s) to an existing Collection, click the
                            <b>Add to an existing Collection</b>
                            radio button. A list of Collections that you are allowed to modify is displayed.
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            Click the <b>Replace current objects</b> checkbox if you want to overwrite the contents
                            of the existing Collection.
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            The list of existing Collections can be filtered by name, sharing permissions and favorite
                            status. To filter by name, type the required Collection name in the filter box. To filter by
                            permissions, select the <b>All</b>, <b>Public</b>, or <b>Private</b> buttons. Click the
                            <b>Favorites</b>
                            button to view favorites.
                        </li>
                        <li>
                            Click on a Collection name to select that Collection.
                        </li>
                    </ol>
                </info>
            </step>
            <step id="3">
                <cmd>Save a Collection</cmd>
                <info>
                    <p>
                        <ol>
                            <li>
                                Click the <b>Add</b> button to save the Collection.
                            </li>
                        </ol>
                    </p>
                </info>
            </step>
        </steps>
        <result>
            <p>
                <ol>
                    <li>
                        A saved notification is displayed and the Collection name is displayed in the Network Panel under
                        the Collections Tab.
                        <p>Note : Refresh Network Explorer for latest Information in Network Panel.</p>
                    </li>
                </ol>
            </p>
        </result>
    </taskbody>
</task>